robo.to 2012-10-03

# Robo.to

**PARTICLE PROGRAMMATICA PRIVACY POLICY**

    Particle Programmatica has created this privacy statement ("Privacy Policy") to explain and summarize how we collect, use and protect, or in some cases do not protect, your personal information as you interact with us online through the website (the "Website").  Particle Programmatica reserves the right to change this Privacy Policy at any time by posting a new privacy statement at this location.  Therefore, you are responsible for periodically checking the Privacy Policy for changes.  Your use of the Website is governed at all times by the Particle Programmatica Terms and Conditions of Use.  If you are visiting from outside the United States there may be special rules or limitations on your use of this Website.  
    
    **1.	INFORMATION WE COLLECT** 
    
    Particle Programmatica collects and uses information you provide to us or that we learn from your use of this Website.  Particle Programmatica does not share your personal information with third parties for their direct marketing purposes.  We may share your personal information where it is necessary for us to complete a transaction or do something that you have asked us to do.  Whenever we may need to share your personal information, we try to provide you with the information you need to make informed choices.  
    
    Particle Programmatica collects and uses personal information from you in several ways: 
    
    User Accounts.  In order to access certain areas of the Website, you may be required to create a user account and/or provide certain personal information such as your name, your email address, your telephone number, your address, your birth date, your gender, and other personal information.  With your consent, we may also use the information you provide in online registration forms to notify you periodically about important changes to the Website (such as a change to this Privacy Policy or notice of a security breach), new Particle Programmatica products and services, and special offers and contests that may be of interest to you.  Regardless of any other provision of this Privacy Policy, we will permanently store any personal information provided by you via such registration process.  
    
    Where you provide optional information, such as information about your interests and hobbies, Particle Programmatica only uses this information on an aggregate basis to enable us to better understand our users, develop new products, and improve our products and services.  Where practical, Particle Programmatica limits the access of our service providers and vendors who assist with technical support and customer service through the use of confidentiality provisions and agreements that are intended to enforce this Privacy Policy.
    
    Website Usage.  Particle Programmatica, or Particle Programmatica authorized service providers, may observe your activities, preferences, and transactional data (such as your IP address and browser type) relating to your use of this Website.  While we may collect or log this information, we generally do not identify you or match this information with your other personal information.  We may use this collected or logged information to diagnose website technical problems, to facilitate your use of the site, or to track aggregate traffic patterns throughout the Website.  
    
    Online Transactions.  If we offer you the opportunity to purchase products online and you choose to purchase such products, you may be asked to share personal information in addition to the information provided to create a user account, such as credit card information, in order to complete a transaction.  In addition, you may be asked for information needed to complete your order, contact you to confirm the order, and provide related customer service.  This information is used, for example, to effect your transactions, to create and share aggregate reports about these transactions, and to perform credit fraud screening services for transactions between you and Particle Programmatica and/or our authorized service providers.  
    
    Recruitment and Job Applications.  You may provide us with personal information, such as that contained on a resume or a curriculum vitae, in connection with a job application or inquiry.  We may use this information throughout Particle Programmatica (worldwide) for the purpose of employment consideration or your inquiry.  We may keep your information on file for a reasonable period of time for future consideration.
    
    Public Areas.  Any information disclosed in public areas of the Website will become public information.  We cannot control the use of information disclosed in public forums, such as bulletin boards, news groups, communication facilities and chat rooms.  You should exercise caution when disclosing information in these public areas and should refrain from disclosing your personal information.  Please remember that any information that is disclosed in these areas, including your name, becomes available to the public and you should exercise caution when deciding to disclose your personal information.
    
    Particle Programmatica WILL TREAT ANY MESSAGE BOARD POSTINGS, FEEDBACK, EMAILS OR SUGGESTIONS YOU PROVIDE TO US AS NON-CONFIDENTIAL AND NON-PROPRIETARY.  IF YOU CHOOSE TO USE YOUR REAL NAME, YOUR NAME WILL BE AVAILABLE TO AND VIEWABLE BY ANYONE USING THE WORLD WIDE WEB AND/OR USING A SEARCH ENGINE.
    
    **2.	USE OF COLLECTED INFORMATION**
    
    Certain Third Party Transactions.  Particle Programmatica may work with some authorized service providers to provide technical and customer support, shipping, credit card processing, product fulfillment or other services.  Where practical, Particle Programmatica shall require these service providers to safeguard personal information you provide to us.  To the extent it is necessary for these service providers to complete their contractual obligations to Particle Programmatica, these third parties may have access to or process your personal information.  Particle Programmatica generally limits their use of your personal information to the purpose for which it was shared.  Particle Programmatica may sometimes permit our authorized service providers to have access to aggregate statistics about our customers, sales, traffic patterns, and related site information.  
    
    Mergers, Acquisitions and Bankruptcy.  If Particle Programmatica should ever file for bankruptcy or merge with another company, or if Particle Programmatica should decide to buy, sell or reorganize some part or all of its business, Particle Programmatica may be required to disclose your personal information to prospective or actual purchasers or receive personal information from sellers.  It is Particle Programmatica's practice to seek appropriate protection for information disclosed or received in these types of transactions.
    
    As Required by Law and Other Extraordinary Disclosures.  Particle Programmatica may be required to disclose your personal information if it: (a) believes it is reasonably necessary to comply with legal process (such as a court order, subpoena, search warrant, etc.) or other legal requirements of any governmental authority; (b) would potentially mitigate our liability in an actual or potential lawsuit; (c) is otherwise necessary to protect our rights or property; or (d) is necessary protect the interest of other users of our Website.
    
    **3.	CHILDREN**
    
    Particle Programmatica does not knowingly collect or solicit personal information from anyone under the age of 13 or knowingly allow such persons to register.  If you are under 13, you should not attempt to register for the Website or send information about yourself to us, including your name, address, telephone number, or email address.  No one under age 13 may provide any personal information to or on the Website.  If a child under 13 submits information through any part of the Website without verification of parental consent, and we learn the person submitting the information is a child or such consent has not been verified, we will attempt to delete this information as soon as possible.  Because we do not knowingly collect any personal information from children under 13, we do not use or disclose such information to third parties.  If you believe that Particle Programmatica may have any information about a child under 13, please contact us at [info@particularplace.com](mailto:info@particularplace.com).
    
    **4.	SECURITY**
    
    No data transmissions over the Internet can be guaranteed to be 100% secure.  Consequently, we cannot ensure or warrant the security of any information you transmit to us and you do so at your own risk.  Once we receive your transmission, we make reasonable efforts to ensure security on our systems.  We use secure server software (SSL) and firewalls to protect your information from unauthorized access, disclosure, alteration, or destruction.  However, please note that this is not a guarantee that such information may not be accessed, disclosed, altered or destroyed by breach of such firewalls and secure server software.  Particle Programmatica is not responsible for circumvention of any privacy settings or security measures contained on the Website.  
    
    You understand and acknowledge that, even after removal, copies of your information may remain viewable in cashed or archived pages or if other users who you permitted to access your information have copied or stored your information.
    
    If Particle Programmatica learns of a security systems breach we may attempt to notify you electronically so that you can take appropriate protective steps.  By using this Website or providing personal information to us, you agree that we can communicate with you electronically regarding security, privacy and administrative issues relating to your use of the Website.  Particle Programmatica may post a notice on our Website if a security breach occurs.  If this happens, you will need a web browser enabling you to view the Website.  Particle Programmatica may also send an email to you at the email address you have provided to us in these circumstances.  Depending on where you live, you may have a legal right to receive notice of a security breach in writing.  To receive free written notice of a security breach (or to withdraw your consent from receiving electronic notice) you should notify us at [info@particularplace.com](mailto:info@particularplace.com).
    
    **5.	INTERNATIONAL VISITORS AND CUSTOMERS** 
    
    Particle Programmatica Worldwide.  Because Particle Programmatica operates globally, circumstances could arise where it is necessary for us to make your personal information available to our worldwide business units.  Privacy laws differ across the globe.  If it is necessary for the purposes for which you have shared personal information with us for us to share your information within Particle Programmatica's global operations, we will do so consistent with this Privacy Policy.  For example, necessary transfers of European Union customer personal information will be made consistent with the European Union Safe Harbor (see below).
    
    This Website is hosted in the United States and is intended for United States visitors.  If you are visiting from the European Union or other regions with laws governing data collection and use that may differ from United States law, please note that you are transferring your personal data to the United States and by providing your personal data you consent to that transfer.  When you provide personal data to Particle Programmatica or our service providers or vendors, you consent to the processing of your data in the United States as the Website is operated in the United States.
    
    European Union Safe Harbor Adherence.  Particle Programmatica adheres to the Safe Harbor principles negotiated between the United States and the European Union regarding data protection with regard to customer data and personal data Particle Programmatica receives when providing technical and customer support.  Accordingly, when visiting this web site or providing personal data to Particle Programmatica through our technical or customer support, Particle Programmatica has taken steps to ensure the adequate protection of the processing of your personal data.
    
    Parts of this Privacy Policy may not apply to visitors from outside the United States because certain services are not offered to those outside the United States.
    
    **6.	LINKS TO THIRD-PARTY SITES AND CO-BRANDED WEBSITES**
    
    This Website may contain links to third-party sites, however, please be aware that Particle Programmatica is not responsible for and cannot control the privacy practices of these other sites.  We encourage you to read the privacy policies for these other sites, as they may differ from ours.
    
    This Website may contain links to co-branded web sites that may display Particle Programmatica's logo and trademarks but which are maintained by third parties.  Please read the privacy policy on the co-branded site for the applicable privacy practices relating to personal information collected via that site, as it may differ from this Privacy Policy.  This Privacy Policy applies solely to personal information collected by Particle Programmatica.  
    
    Advertisements that appear on the Website are sometimes delivered (or "served") directly to users by third party advertisers.  Such third parties automatically receive your IP address when this happens.  These third party advertisers may also download cookies to your computer, or use other technologies such as JavaScript and "web beacons" (also known as "1x1 gifs") to measure the effectiveness of their ads and to personalize advertising content.  Doing this allows the advertising network to recognize your computer each time they send you an advertisement in order to measure the effectiveness of their ads and to personalize advertising content.  In this way, they may compile information about where individuals using your computer or browser saw their advertisements and determine which advertisements are clicked.  Particle Programmatica does not have access to or control of the cookies that may be placed by the third party advertisers.  Third party advertisers have no access to your contact information stored on the Website unless you choose to share it with them.
    
    This Privacy Policy covers the use of cookies by Particle Programmatica and does not cover the use of cookies or other tracking technologies by any of its advertisers.
    
    **7.	CONTACT PREFERENCES**
    
    When you provide Particle Programmatica with personal information, if you allow us, we may communicate with you by the method you choose about topics of your choosing.  Particle Programmatica seeks your consent to receive marketing communications from us when you provide your personal information. 
    
    Generally, when we contact you, we will try to provide you with an easy and convenient way to notify us if you would not like further similar communications.  
    
    **8.	CONTACTING PARTICLE PROGRAMMATICA**
    
    If you have any questions, comments, or concerns about this Privacy Policy, or would like to make changes to your personal information or contact preferences, or delete personal information you have provided to us, please email us at [info@particularplace.com](mailto:info@particularplace.com).
    
    Postal Mail Address:
    Particle Programmatica 
    360 Ritch Street, 3rd Floor
    San Francisco, CA 94107
    
    If you have a privacy concern regarding Particle Programmatica or this Privacy Policy and if you cannot satisfactorily resolve it through the use of this Website you should then write to [info@particularplace.com](mailto:info@particularplace.com).  In the event that we are still unable to resolve your concerns Particle Programmatica is committed to cooperating to achieve a proper resolution of your privacy concerns.
    
    Copyright © 2010 Particle Programmatica.  All Rights Reserved.  
    
    Effective Date: July 2, 2008
    Previous Modification: July 2, 2008
